# CIRINO LOMBARDI

# Full Stack Developer

@ cirino940630@gmail.com

#### SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer with 6 years of experience who is early adaptive and follows a trend always. My experience as a web developer at several companies gave me a strong knowledge of traditional web technologies and new coming latest technologies. I am looking to join forces to continue to grow my skill set while contributing to the positive outcome of making people richer, smarter, happier.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Full Stack Developer

Overflow 06/2022 - 02/2023 Japan

- Created an application interface that integrated 35 third-party APIs and improved sales results by 80% within 3 weeks on the job.
- Wrote 200+ unit tests to verify the functionality of user interfaces, back-end processing, connectivity, and relational database interactions.
- Implemented software design patterns and best practices, resulting in a 25% reduction in software issues.
- Revamped website flows and navigation menus, reducing the frequency of misdirected customer service queries by 30% and increasing traffic to previously neglected pages.

### Blockchain Developer

Vegas One Realty 12/2020 - 06/2022 Singapore

- Spearheaded the design and development of the NFT deployer, resulting in a 40% increase in efficiency in deploying non-fungible tokens on various blockchain platforms.
- Successfully implemented over 20 smart contracts and decentralized applications, resulting in a 60% reduction in transaction processing time and a 75% reduction in gas fees.
- Utilized coding, cryptography, and security skills to ensure the secure and seamless operation of the NFT Deployer, resulting in a 90% decrease in the number of security incidents reported by users.

# Full Stack Developer

HBLAB JSC 07/2019 - 12/2020 Japan

- Improved performance by resolving more than 80 critical bugs in the company's products.
- Reduced development time by 70% through code reuse in jQuery libraries for various projects with over 1.8K combined page visits.
- Increased daily traffic from 35% to 80% by repairing existing websites to improve user experience and incorporated SEO.

# Front End Developer

Trust Recruit Pte. Ltd 07/2018 - 06/2019 Singapore

- Created a user interface as a single-page application using React and Redux, which increased the productivity of 7K users by 72%.
- Worked with another two developers to implement RESTful APIs in Django that enabled the analytical team of five to increase reporting speed by 20%.
- Led the integration of a customer service chat functionality to answer user questions and schedule consultations, resulting in a 15% increase in leads.

#### EDUCATION

## Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science and Design(CSD)

Singapore University of Technology and Design(SUTD)

04/2014 - 03/2018 Singapore, Singapore

React.js	Vue.js	Node.js	Express.
MongoDB	MERN stack MEVN stack		
Python	Django	Solidity	Web3
MySQL	Laravel	JavaScript	CSS
рнр н	TML C	/C++	

LANGUAGES		
English	Proficient	••••
Chinese	Advanced	••••

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **MERN Hubbers**

http://hubbers.io

This site is a community of makers that create, develop, produce and sell innovative or not so innovative products through the power of the crowd. It allows anyone to bring an innovative product idea from concept to successful profitable business with minimum resources.

### MEVN Capsho

https://www.capsho.com

This site is an Al Copywriting tool designed for Podcasters. It will help you reach more listeners across ALL platforms while saving you HOURS per episode.

# Auto Sign Up, Sending Ticket For BuyRealFollows

https://www.buyrealfollows.com

This site is based on a PHP microservice that implements automatic sign-up to corresponding sites and sends tickets.

# Server-side Rendering Template

 $\label{lem:https://github.com/SuperBluestar/react-router-express-ssrtemplate} \\$ 

I made very useful template for implementing server-side rendering in React easily.

#### NFT Deployer

https://github.com/SuperBluestar/nft-project
Handles the deployment of NFT contracts as well as
minting of NFTs on said contracts.

# Django E-commerce

https://github.com/SuperBluestar/django-ecommerce
This site displays products. Users can add and remove
products to/from their cart while also specifying the
quantity of each item. They can then enter their address
and choose Stripe to handle the payment processing.